▲ ABOUT ME

I have been working in IT for 10 years, I am getting specialized in Java development to enhance my working base and progress within the industry.

I am a Team player always striving to develop personally and professionally by accepting every new challenge, networking with other industry professionals and consistently placing client solutions, satisfaction and service at the forefront of operations.

- xavier.lamourec@gmail.com
- +353 83 88 46758
- https://github.com/xbreizh
- **₩** JAVA
 - Spring • •
 - Struts •
 - Hibernate • •
 - Web Services • •
 - Junit Mockito • •
- ₩ CI CD
 - Git • •
 - Jenkins • •
 - SonarQube • •
- **₩** DATABASE
 - Oracle / postgreSql • •
- **Ψ** FRONT-END

html / css / javascript • • •

XAVIER LAMOUREC

JAVA DEVELOPER JUNIOR (French)

WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST

En Smartfocus

2017 – 2019

RESPONSIBILITIES

UI Support / Training

Data Support: Database management / basic shell and SQL scripts API Support: Assisting clients with company API usage (REST/SOAP)

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ANALYST

En Smartfocus

2013 - 2017

RESPONSIBILITIES

Technical assistance for a complex emailing platform CSS /Html / email campaign creation / Segment / Report

SUPPORT DESK AGENT

In Accenture

2012 – 2013

RESPONSIBILITIES

Technical assistance for company workers

LEVEL 2 - SERVICE DESK AGENT

En CPL company; Hewlett Packard Client

2010 – 2012

RESPONSIBILITIES

Resolving complex technical issues and handling escalations and complaints Mentored new staff / outage management

Worked across various technologies: Windows Servers; Active Directory, SCCM, Citrix; VPN, IPhone and Blackberry, Lotus Note

EDUCATION

JAVA DEVELOPER PATH TRAINING

Open Classrooms, Academy of Paris

2018 - Current

DESIGN PATTERNS, STRUTS, SPRING, HIBERNATE, GIT, DOCKER, JENKINS, SONARQUBE, JAXWS, SQL, JAVASCRIPT (GITHUB)

MASTER OF SCIENCES (STAPS)

university of Corsica

≐ 2007



LANGUAGES

FRENCH ENGLISH ROM

ROMANIAN SPANISH